Contact

Cranford, New Jersey michael.gedonius@hotmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/ michaelgedonius (LinkedIn) www.wsjoffice.com (Company)

Top Skills

Digital Media Advertising Digital Strategy

Michael Gedonius

Integrated Media Sales Professional

Greater New York City Area

Summary

20 year media sales and management professional with a proven track record of success spanning across print, digital, mobile, out of home, and streaming radio.

Specialized focus on building large cross-platfrom marketing solutions for Fortune 200 partners.

Experience

Taboola Senior Sales Manager January 2017 - Present Greater New York City Area

Open Road Integrated Media Inc. VP, National Sales March 2016 - December 2016 (10 months) Greater New York City Area

Playboy Enterprises Account Director March 2015 - February 2016 (1 year)

Vigorously represented media sales for Playboy across Print, Digital, Mobile and Events and was part of the launch team for Playboy's major re-branding (aka - no more nudity) of Playboy Magazine.

Apple

Account Executive

October 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 5 months)

iAd and iTunes Radio reaches millions of iPhone, iPad and iPod Touch users around the world in their favorite apps. With the iAd Network, you get access to the Apple audience, the world's most engaged, passionate and loyal consumer.

Wall Street Journal Office Network
Executive Director of Sales & Digital Development
May 2010 - October 2013 (3 years 6 months)
New York, NY

The Wall Street Journal Office Network is the premier at-work marketing platform. Along with our strategic partner, Dow Jones, we have built a network of 760+ premier office buildings concentrated in the top 15 markets reaching 1MM+ business managers and professionals every day.

TMZ.com

East Coast Account Executive July 2009 - May 2010 (11 months)

Aggressively representing the biggest and baddest celebrity/pop culture website on the planet.

Alpha Media Group East Coast Director 2008 - 2009 (2 years)

Managed a stellar group of senior sales professionals from Boston to Miami with 20 million in annual sales. In addition, I also covered a key list of top advertisers including Verizon and Pepsi

Dennis Publishing Account Executive 2006 - 2008 (3 years)

Wenner Media Account Executive 2000 - 2006 (7 years)

Travel Weekly Account Executive 1997 - 2000 (4 years)

Education

Purdue University
BS, Advertising/Communications

Purdue University

Bachelor's degree, Advertising